Guide to the Orrin Sage Wightman Collection [1895-1945] PR 94
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series 6: American Red Cross Mission to Russia
  - Subseries 7: Manuscript of Diary of an American Physician in the Russian Revolution
    A typed manuscript copy of Wightman's published account of his trip to Russia. Handwritten editing and notes are present, although it seems to be a finalized copy of the manuscript. This was originally in a binder, but has been removed and is now divided into two folders. The New-York Historical Society holds a published copy of this work.
    - Manuscript of Diary of an American Physician in the Russian Revolution (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Manuscript of Diary of an American Physician in the Russian Revolution (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 8: Ledger of film titles
    A seemingly complete listing of titles for moving pictures taken by Wightman and his crew. Many of these scenes were also still photographed, his descriptions in this ledger may supplement information elsewhere about locations or actions. This document was originally housed in a binder, the front of which has been photocopied and is in the folder with the manuscript. The physical binder, now empty, is housed in Box 30 along with this folder.
    - Ledger of film titles (Box 30, Folder 3)